{
    "id": "0abeba0873ab4894bb694326dfc6cdcb",
    "title": "Change Into Active Voice",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This portrait was painted by my grandmother. / My grandmother ........................ this portrait.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "painted",
                "has painted",
                "had painted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured boy was taken to the hospital. / They ..................... the injured boy to the hospital.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have taken",
                "took",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been sacked. / They .......................... her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sacked",
                "have sacked",
                "are sacked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been invited to their party. / They ............................ me to their party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "have invited",
                "had invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been promoted. / They .......................... her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "promoted",
                "have promoted",
                "had promoted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog was beaten by its master. / The master .................... the dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beaten",
                "had beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was run over by a speeding car. / A speeding car ........................ over him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "ran",
                "had run"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The flowers have been plucked by the children. / The children .......................... the flowers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plucked",
                "have plucked",
                "had plucked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My pen has been stolen. / Somebody ........................... my pen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stole",
                "stolen",
                "has stolen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The house is being built by the masons. / Masons ............................ the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "built",
                "build",
                "are building"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Short stories are written by her. / She ...................... short stories.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writes",
                "is writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief has been arrested by the police. / The police ........................... the thief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has arrested",
                "have arrested",
                "arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}